hi! my name is **Victoria trac**

CONTACT |

victoriatrac.com victoriatrac@gmail.com (404) 981-9036 Denver, Colorado

i want to work with you!

Technically skilled, creative problem solver with an insatiable want to learn. Adept at iterative and user-centered design, with knowledge in all aspects of 2D and 3D production pipelines. Constantly striving for efficiency, accuracy, and consistency. Passionate, hard-working, and self-motivated team player with proven interpersonal and research expertise.

EDUCATION

Lambda School Full-Stack Web Development October 2020 - present

Savannah College of Art and Design Interactive Design and Game Development, B.F.A. September 2013 - December 2017

EMPLOYMENT

Freelance Visual Art and Design 2014 - present

Create fine art and digital works on a commission basis. Apply color theory and lighting techniques in illustrations to convey realism. Manage time effectively while working independently.

Interior Designer @ Havenly March 2019 - August 2020

Consulted with clients to create initial design pitches through final renderings (e.g. floor plans and 2D mockups) based on their feedback, budget, and style. Produced designs for over 200 rooms.

Additional: Temp. 3D lighting, 7 years retail, 3 years instructional

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#, Java, Python, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, MEL Script, Arnold OSL, Renderman SL

Tools: Maya, Mudbox, NukeX, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, After Effects, XD, Unity, Unreal, GitHub, Bash